{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831964309","data":{"timestamp":" 946831964309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831970155","data":{"timestamp":" 946831970155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" START_KAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831971188","data":{"timestamp":" 946831971188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831972755","data":{"timestamp":" 946831972754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831975102","data":{"timestamp":" 946831975102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831976710","data":{"timestamp":" 946831976709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831978995","data":{"timestamp":" 946831978994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831980615","data":{"timestamp":" 946831980615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831984549","data":{"timestamp":" 946831984548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831986134","data":{"timestamp":" 946831986134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831989593","data":{"timestamp":" 946831989593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831991160","data":{"timestamp":" 946831991159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831995091","data":{"timestamp":" 946831995090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831996710","data":{"timestamp":" 946831996710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946831999647","data":{"timestamp":" 946831999647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832001252","data":{"timestamp":" 946832001251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832003877","data":{"timestamp":" 946832003877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832005479","data":{"timestamp":" 946832005478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832013452","data":{"timestamp":" 946832013452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832015062","data":{"timestamp":" 946832015061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832019477","data":{"timestamp":" 946832019477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832021490","data":{"timestamp":" 946832021489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832021611","data":{"timestamp":" 946832021611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 0de6df32-686e-45a8-987a-2bb7820fa239"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832048467","data":{"timestamp":" 946832048467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kato"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832049546","data":{"timestamp":" 946832049545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kato"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832052761","data":{"timestamp":" 946832052761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832053800","data":{"timestamp":" 946832053799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832056209","data":{"timestamp":" 946832056208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832057260","data":{"timestamp":" 946832057259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832060151","data":{"timestamp":" 946832060151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832061203","data":{"timestamp":" 946832061202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832064460","data":{"timestamp":" 946832064459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832065514","data":{"timestamp":" 946832065514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832070600","data":{"timestamp":" 946832070600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832071650","data":{"timestamp":" 946832071649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832076091","data":{"timestamp":" 946832076090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832077149","data":{"timestamp":" 946832077148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832080218","data":{"timestamp":" 946832080217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832081288","data":{"timestamp":" 946832081287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832085475","data":{"timestamp":" 946832085474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832086534","data":{"timestamp":" 946832086533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832089271","data":{"timestamp":" 946832089270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832090328","data":{"timestamp":" 946832090327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832093787","data":{"timestamp":" 946832093785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832093924","data":{"timestamp":" 946832093924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 75ec6d30-d323-497c-b66a-7cba4ed8f6cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ka.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832132120","data":{"timestamp":" 946832132120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832144380","data":{"timestamp":" 946832144380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832155533","data":{"timestamp":" 946832155533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832163574","data":{"timestamp":" 946832163574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832166806","data":{"timestamp":" 946832166806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832177837","data":{"timestamp":" 946832177837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832180636","data":{"timestamp":" 946832180636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832191998","data":{"timestamp":" 946832191998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832199578","data":{"timestamp":" 946832199578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832201963","data":{"timestamp":" 946832201962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832223000","data":{"timestamp":" 946832223000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832231055","data":{"timestamp":" 946832231055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832233302","data":{"timestamp":" 946832233302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832247946","data":{"timestamp":" 946832247946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832255186","data":{"timestamp":" 946832255186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832257383","data":{"timestamp":" 946832257383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832268563","data":{"timestamp":" 946832268563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832272619","data":{"timestamp":" 946832272619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832288661","data":{"timestamp":" 946832288660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832291436","data":{"timestamp":" 946832291436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832301357","data":{"timestamp":" 946832301357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832304067","data":{"timestamp":" 946832304067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832331379","data":{"timestamp":" 946832331379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832340985","data":{"timestamp":" 946832340984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832348079","data":{"timestamp":" 946832348079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832356899","data":{"timestamp":" 946832356899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832385964","data":{"timestamp":" 946832385964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832410453","data":{"timestamp":" 946832410453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 3e1da760-d37f-4e3e-a441-9cd80eb24b2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832449539","data":{"timestamp":" 946832449539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832457020","data":{"timestamp":" 946832457020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832459327","data":{"timestamp":" 946832459326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832490743","data":{"timestamp":" 946832490742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832497750","data":{"timestamp":" 946832497750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832499180","data":{"timestamp":" 946832499180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832506477","data":{"timestamp":" 946832506476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832518270","data":{"timestamp":" 946832518270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946832531271","data":{"timestamp":" 946832531271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_195224"," gameId":" 7cd1d046-ec39-417c-bafe-d39147588970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}